Do whatever you want with the Merry.
I won't let anything hold us back.
We're getting a new ship and sailing forward.
So long, Usopp.
It was fun.
Well, it lasted.
You can't doubt yourself.
In times like these, if you lose your confidence,
then who can we have faith in?
Let's pack our things and go.
You know as well as me
that after tonight, we can never return to this ship again.
Severe shock hits the City of Water.
Iceberg targeted.
Who was the first to find him?
Could they please answer a few questions for us?
Who's the culprit?
Are there any suspects?
Is there any connection between this and the annihilation of the Frankie house?
What's the condition?
Could you give us a statement, please?
Hey, did you hear about what happened at the shipbuilding island last night?
Is it true?
Did he die?
Frankie did this.
I just know it.
You let someone like that run around free and this is what happened.
Well, it might have been those pirates
who've been hanging around the shipyards the past few days.
Word is there was an explosion out at the Cape last night.
Do you think there's a connection?
I don't know for sure,
but there have been a few pirates fighting with the foreman recently.
So this is where you've been.
We went through all the trouble of renting a room and no one's using it.
I guess nobody could sleep, huh?
And where's Luffy?
Over there.
So, where were you?
Hmm?
I kept lookout around the Rocky Cape all night.
I wanted to be there in case Robin came back.
Oh.
She never said anything about leaving.
I wonder where she went.
Ever since we got to this island,
it's been one bad thing after another.
Our money was stolen,
and then there's everything that happened to poor Usopp.
He's injured.
He could barely even stand up.
And by now, on top of everything else,
he's probably got a fever.
Chopper.
That's enough, okay?
Don't talk about him anymore.
I think I'll try looking around for her in town today.
Do you think we're gonna find her?
Who knows?
It's not like I have any place specific in mind to check out.
I just feel certain that she's still here somewhere.
If anything should happen,
we should use this inn as our meet-up point.
I want to help.
I'm gonna come, too.
All right, then.
Come on.
Luffy!
Nami, what's wrong?
It's awful.
The whole city's talking about it.
Luffy, listen to me.
Last night, something terrible happened to Iceberg.
Iceberg was shot in his home.
Stop screwing around!
Is this some kind of joke?
No joke.
Is he alive?
Who would do such a thing?
Everyone loves him!
Yes, he's alive.
Calm down, Polly.
Listen to me for a second.
Okay?
He was discovered in his room early this morning,
lying in a pool of his own blood.
Like I said, he's alive,
but he's been unconscious since he was found.
You need to come to the main office immediately.
Lulu, where's Polly?
I just called him.
He'll be here soon.
Good.
Reporters are all over the place.
It's mass hysteria out there.
We are the ones who'd like to know what happened.
The office has been torn apart,
but there's no trace of anything being stolen.
No money, no valuables, nothing.
If this wasn't a robbery,
then the question is,
who would try to kill Iceberg and why?
Hmm.
At any rate, we're in big trouble here.
The city's in total panic.
If anything should happen to Iceberg,
then it's not only the end for the Galilaw Company,
but the entire city of Water 7 as well.
Doctor, please.
What is his condition?
He was shot two times in the front
and another three from behind.
I have no idea what happened in that room last night,
but whatever it was, it was brutal.
According to forensics,
there's no sign of the locks being picked to his office
or anywhere else in the building.
The incident occurred in a room
no one could have entered.
The only thing out of place they found
was a mask you can buy just about anywhere.
Ice pops from the shipyard?
Yes.
I've heard he's still unconscious.
I thought everybody in this entire city loved that guy.
Why him?
Who are you talking about?
He's the nice man that helped us out so much yesterday.
The president of the shipbuilding company
as well as the mayor of Water 7.
Hmm.
Sounds like an important guy.
Yeah.
It's pretty much the worst thing
that could have happened to this town.
I'll go check on him.
Luffy, wait up!
I'm coming too!
On that note, let's go look for Robin.
Come on, chopper.
What about you?
Well, I think I'll just wait a while
to see how things turn out.
Extra! Extra!
Read all about it!
Iceberg, our beloved mayor
and the hero of Water 7
has fallen victim to the hands of an assassin!
This is an urgent news report
covering the incident!
This is terrible.
Is Iceberg okay?
How awful!
Who would do such a thing?
Hey, give me one of those!
Who did it?
It doesn't say.
No clue.
You with the newspapers.
There's some crucial information missing here.
What's the deal?
Doesn't anybody know anything?
What's going on?
Only pirates would pull a vicious attack
like that out of nowhere.
No doubt about it.
I'd like to get my hands on the ones that did it.
There were a bunch of pirates
rampaging through Doc 1 just yesterday.
You mean the Mikazuki gang?
I know it sounds crazy,
but I think the government did this.
What?
What are you saying?
I'm talking about Corgi.
Every time he comes to talk with Iceberg,
he gets rejected and leaves.
I'm telling you, Frankie did it!
I don't really know what he's trying to speak with him about,
but he must have done this out of spite.
I'd keep that theory to myself.
If you openly blame the world government,
it won't be taken lightly.
Is this diabolical criminal's goal
to gain wealth or power?
Who is this nameless assassin
that disappeared without a trace?
Who in the hell did this?
I'm not going to let him get away with it!
Thank you for writing this feature.
Next stop, the station at War 7.
Arriving momentarily.
The End
Paulie!
A word, please!
Can we get a comment about this incident?
What were you told before you came here?
Shut up, all of you.
Get the hell out of my way.
Tell us, what explanation were you given by your company?
Paulie, please, a comment!
I don't have time for this crap! Get out of here!
Are you aware of any incident that could cause someone to target Iceberg's life? Anything at all?
There must be something!
Any altercations with Paulie?
Pirates, Paulie, won't you please?
Didn't you idiots hear me?!
Get out of here!
Whoopie!
Gare!
Studying is burning with the birds of the cielo.
Bip!
What arous olha is fast!
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
Good. Then let's get going.
Take a look. It's all about Iceberg.
So I guess the rumors are true. He was attacked.
Yeah. So if we go to the shipyard, it's likely we won't be able to meet with him.
Then let's just go to his house.
I believe he lives inside the main office.
Eh.
Huh?
I'm a cuss, I'm weak.
They took, they took all the money and could face the others now.
We were finally able to mix the berry.
Nami, what are you thinking about?
It's nothing.
Kiwi.
もず.
Am...
kiwi mozu am am i asleep is this a dream this is no dream without a doubt this is the very spot
where the frankie house stood but something like this happening just seems so extreme
what the hell is going on
who would be stupid enough to do something like this to my house
hold on i know who damn you straw hat luffy so this is your payback for us stealing your 200 million
berries how dare you treat my faithful men this way it's so heartless unforgivable
frankie bro you came back frankie you guys are all right what a relief thank goodness
it was terrible those pirates are completely insane
listen we've been keeping track of what the straw hats are up to we know there's no way you're gonna
let them get away with this where are they now it's all going to an end after that they headed
over to the ship building island it's dark one they were there yesterday i bet that's where they're
going is that so all right then straw hat luffy when i find you i'm gonna rip you apart
the southern wind huh
the waves are getting rough too if this keeps up the sea train won't be able to run tonight
get ready we're going back to the island okay
aqua laguna is coming
your attention please your attention please this is the water 7 weather forecasting center
as of now an aqua laguna severe weather warning has just been issued for the entire island
its arrival time is estimated to be sometime between midnight and 12 30. oh yeah i guess it is about that
time i've been preoccupied with what happened to iceberg hey aqua laguna is coming make sure everybody
knows about the warning all right no more work for today aqua laguna oh excuse me what was that broadcast
about just now what do you mean everybody knows what oh wait are you a visitor here sorry you've come
sightseeing sightseeing at a really bad time aqua laguna is an annual storm it's about to pass through
here a storm huh a big one you're gonna need to evacuate to higher ground this entire city will be
underwater soon underwater really don't worry it's not gonna happen right this second according to the
forecast it'll arrive sometime around midnight the locals have gotten used to it and you'll remember
see ya later hmm the whole town will be uh wait it's gonna sink yeah apparently so we need to find robin
and quick come on right by the way where do you think we should look for her good question where would
she likely go around here hmm let's see ancient ruins maybe nope nothing like that in this place where
else uh is there anything she likes ancient ruins stop saying that there aren't any here fine then you
tell me what else she likes i asked you because i don't know hey don't get in front of me got it
huh when you think about it we really don't know that much about robin do we
can't you tell us anything hey iceberg what happened here what's going on
can't go that way man we're never gonna find out what's going on unless we find some way to get to
ice pops um excuse me can you tell me where the entrance of the main office is yeah it's head dock
one but i don't think you're gonna have any luck getting in with everything that happened here they're
only allowing authorized personnel to get through you're not alone everyone wants it we're all so
worried about him i see thank you look at all those people what's all the commotion about well the bigger
the audience the better i always say
no don't tell me it's that rhythm what why now hey guys question did you just say my name no we didn't just
go away come on everybody no need to be shy say my name we don't want to get lost you're the one who
attacked iceberg aren't you yeah he has to be just leave get the hell out of here hang that got
fighting on that punk what a bunch of noisy flies i'm water seven's number one super guy the face of the
underworld and you know why i'm the man with the plan the power and fame and people everywhere call
out my name wow
come out and show yourself
new
me
you
On the next, One Piece, Gum Gum Human versus Fire Breathing Cyborg.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!